[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "Is that -- does that happen?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "--", "does", "that", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Well, maybe.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "maybe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "ECK: What's faith play a role in your life?", "question_tokens": ["ECK", ":", "What", "'s", "faith", "play", "a", "role", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carol Roth", "Newt Gingrich", "Mitch McConnell"]}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "What's wrong with them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "wrong", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Carol Roth, what's the name, Newt Gingrich, Mitch McConnell, you know, everybody that can make my life a living hell as I have a network.", "answer_tokens": ["Carol", "Roth", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "name", ",", "Newt", "Gingrich", ",", "Mitch", "McConnell", ",", "you", "know", ",", "everybody", "that", "can", "make", "my", "life", "a", "living", "hell", "as", "I", "have", "a", "network", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "WDT", ":", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Give me, for instance, what's an example of one of those?", "question_tokens": ["Give", "me", ",", "for", "instance", ",", "what", "'s", "an", "example", "of", "one", "of", "those", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "I think that, you know, you have people that are old in firm that -- and don't have a church, don't have a family, don't have anybody to go to, but that I think is for the local community.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "have", "people", "that", "are", "old", "in", "firm", "that", "--", "and", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "church", ",", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "family", ",", "do", "n't", "have", "anybody", "to", "go", "to", ",", "but", "that", "I", "think", "is", "for", "the", "local", "community", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Is he wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "No ...", "answer_tokens": ["No", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "You seem to delight in identifying heretics?", "question_tokens": ["You", "seem", "to", "delight", "in", "identifying", "heretics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "I mean, who's going to harness that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "who", "'s", "going", "to", "harness", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "It should help all mankind.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "should", "help", "all", "mankind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "We don't want to win?", "question_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Don't care.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Win for what?", "question_tokens": ["Win", "for", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Conservatives don't want to win and it's ...", "answer_tokens": ["Conservatives", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "win", "and", "it", "'s", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "How so, how so?", "question_tokens": ["How", "so", ",", "how", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "He is a progressive.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "a", "progressive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Have you looked into that?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "looked", "into", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Yeah, OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "... where he stands on that?", "question_tokens": ["...", "where", "he", "stands", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Are you comfortable with that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "comfortable", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "The key here is, are you for maximum freedom?", "question_tokens": ["The", "key", "here", "is", ",", "are", "you", "for", "maximum", "freedom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "So, who do -- who would you like for 2016 if you could anoint someone today?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "who", "do", "--", "who", "would", "you", "like", "for", "2016", "if", "you", "could", "anoint", "someone", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "I don't know because I don't trust any of them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "trust", "any", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "You like Ted Cruz a lot?", "question_tokens": ["You", "like", "Ted", "Cruz", "a", "lot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "I like Ted Cruz a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "Ted", "Cruz", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "But can he win or you don't care?", "question_tokens": ["But", "can", "he", "win", "or", "you", "do", "n't", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Who does that if we don't get conservatives elected?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "does", "that", "if", "we", "do", "n't", "get", "conservatives", "elected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Let's see.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nixon"]}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "... assessment of the second term?", "question_tokens": ["...", "assessment", "of", "the", "second", "term", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "... only second to Nixon.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "only", "second", "to", "Nixon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "What's his second term looking like for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "his", "second", "term", "looking", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Because you admit that's a problem, income inequality is real, it's wide and under Obama or no?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "admit", "that", "'s", "a", "problem", ",", "income", "inequality", "is", "real", ",", "it", "'s", "wide", "and", "under", "Obama", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Yeah, I think, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "What's one thing conservative should be talking about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "one", "thing", "conservative", "should", "be", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "You're not going to solve it through government.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "solve", "it", "through", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "How much did we spend?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "did", "we", "spend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "UPP: That's another question, I've seen it.", "answer_tokens": ["UPP", ":", "That", "'s", "another", "question", ",", "I", "'ve", "seen", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 391, "question": "What's your secret?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "secret", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Those are ...", "answer_tokens": ["Those", "are", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What are doing right?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "doing", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 414, "question": "... with TheBlaze TV, so what's the end game?", "question_tokens": ["...", "with", "TheBlaze", "TV", ",", "so", "what", "'s", "the", "end", "game", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "The end game is to be is ubiquity (ph) as possible ...", "answer_tokens": ["The", "end", "game", "is", "to", "be", "is", "ubiquity", "(", "ph", ")", "as", "possible", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Me?", "question_tokens": ["Me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Yes, you.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Never?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Not once.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "once", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "You won't tell us?", "question_tokens": ["You", "wo", "n't", "tell", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I've already talked to God about it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "already", "talked", "to", "God", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "So you think that we as folks with a platform or some level of influence on, have to be more responsible about the kinds of things you've talk about and the way we talk about them?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "think", "that", "we", "as", "folks", "with", "a", "platform", "or", "some", "level", "of", "influence", "on", ",", "have", "to", "be", "more", "responsible", "about", "the", "kinds", "of", "things", "you", "'ve", "talk", "about", "and", "the", "way", "we", "talk", "about", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I think so but I think also, you know, everybody is different, everybody has their own line.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "but", "I", "think", "also", ",", "you", "know", ",", "everybody", "is", "different", ",", "everybody", "has", "their", "own", "line", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Is that a serious question?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "serious", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "It's an attempt to a serious question.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "attempt", "to", "a", "serious", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Glenn"]}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "OK stay with me Glenn.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "stay", "with", "me", "Glenn", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Why are you so fascinated with this old tiny artifact?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "so", "fascinated", "with", "this", "old", "tiny", "artifact", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Because I think that history is -- history has been made in the facts with dates and memorization of names and places where we've lost the story.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "think", "that", "history", "is", "--", "history", "has", "been", "made", "in", "the", "facts", "with", "dates", "and", "memorization", "of", "names", "and", "places", "where", "we", "'ve", "lost", "the", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google Topsy the Elephant"]}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "How so?", "question_tokens": ["How", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Just Google Topsy the Elephant.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "Google", "Topsy", "the", "Elephant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "How do you describe your life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "describe", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Redemption, not survival, redemption.", "answer_tokens": ["Redemption", ",", "not", "survival", ",", "redemption", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Have you encouraged other people into that faith or faith in general?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "encouraged", "other", "people", "into", "that", "faith", "or", "faith", "in", "general", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "No, I find ...", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "find", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Do you find that to be a mission of yours?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "find", "that", "to", "be", "a", "mission", "of", "yours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "No, I find that living a good example and showing people who are miserable, there's an easy -- there's an easier way.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "find", "that", "living", "a", "good", "example", "and", "showing", "people", "who", "are", "miserable", ",", "there", "'s", "an", "easy", "--", "there", "'s", "an", "easier", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]